so let's see if we can figure out what
the problems are with Yuma
aka SMP aka multi-core but suppose we
want to have a lot of course and have
them use decentralized shared memory in
a human SMP fashion which of these our
problems we'll have to face when we do
this first memory needs to be very large
and thus slow for this type of a machine
our main memory will get too many
accesses per second basically we'll need
a huge memory throughput that a normal
memory module will not be able to
provide the next option is we'll need a
lot of small memory modules in
proportion to the number of cores next
our caches will have very small block
sizes and finally the pages for our
virtual memory will become too small to
be usable so select all of those that
are problems for this type of
architecture